# **ANDRES HINCAPIE**

Wakefield, MA 01180 |

Cell: (617) 888-9843 | Email: ahincapievelez@gmail.com

IT manager with 5 years of experience in the sector. Experience working on projects that require solutions for all kinds of tasks, such as implementing technical and computer systems from scratch. Design and implement network architecture to manage networks effectively, efficiently. Web developer with knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, React and database.

Languages: English and Spanish

### **SKILLS**

JavaScript, CSS, HTML, NodeJS, MongoDB, React, Git, GitHub, Zappier, Microsoft365

#### **EDUCATION**

**Per Scholas**, Boston, MA Software Engineer Course April 2023

**Medellin University**, Medellin, Colombia Degree in Telecommunications Engineer June 2013

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Roads Consulting Group, Boston, MA

March 2018 - Current

IT Consultant

- Implement and ensure all of the company's systems are running optimally and at full capacity
- Provide advice on current technology for the company's customers
- Maintain a clear understanding of clients' business needs, and design and implement customize technology solutions
- Training of employees and clients in VoIP systems, CRMs, QuickBooks and Microsoft365.

### **DPV Transportation Inc.,** Everett, MA

May 2016 - July 2022

IT Manager

- Managed mobile applications for customers. The applications allow the customer to track the vehicle in real time, view schedules and receive notifications.
- Provided excellent technical assistance to employees and ensured that the tools they used were working properly.
- Sustain customer satisfaction by resolving issues immediately and presenting data analysis reports using Microsoft BI.

## Boston Project LLC, Winthrop, MA

June 2018 - December 2020

IT Manager

- Manage and administer the technological tools used for the development the employees' tasks and the correct operation of the applications for the customers.
- Assignment and follow up of the different tasks of the projects under development to the employees.
- Technical support of employees' equipment and assistance with bugs in different customer applications.